Use the free code JOINNOW at
www.playships.eu
Then let's play ice hockey!
Inside Out 2
You heard Joy there reporting
straight from Riley's mind-
- and we're expecting a great
fight here today with the Fog Horns.
Riley fans, get up from your
seats and make some noise!
Come on!
Come on, Misty Horn!
Get in with the paws!
Foghorn is number three.
- One two three!
- Fog!
And now it's time to
meet your Tim Riley!
He is playing in his 13th year and will come
straight from the penalty box: Riley's Wrath!
Let me skin him!
Helmet, visor, gloves.
Security check completed.
Everything went smoothly from...
Watch out!
It was Fear, which
kept Riley alert.
We need mouth guards, people.
No, no, no!  It's not ours!
And that's the famous Disgust.
Great, we have him on the team.
- 28, Anderson.  Leg span.
- Oh no.
And the raisins at the end of
the sausage, you know and love him-
- incomparable...
We got an expulsion.
Appropriate!  It's
sad to be home!
Yay.
Andersen got two minutes
in the leg span box.
We have a few minutes,
as Riley sighs.
I'll keep you posted.
Riley is still amazing.
nice.
Not just because he's the
best in class, and he is.
Riley, look here!
He is also very sweet and
caring for street cats.  Frankly!
And now he is officially a teenager.
He got very tall very quickly.
- Have we grown overnight?
- That's our favorite blouse.
We even got braces
with elastics!
- How does it feel?
- Cold!
Excuse me.
Riley's Island of
Personality is in full force.
Although Boybandøen
was destroyed.
But Fjolleøen is
still causing problems.
- Wait, where is Family Island?
- There.
Yes, that's him.
- What's looming over him?
- Friendship Island.  Isn't that beautiful?
But we've discovered that he's a
memory of not just the lowly island.
Getting to the roots
memories also create value.
Homework should be banned.
Rise and Shine is the
best band in the world!
- And my personal favorite...
- I'm a very good friend.
Did you know that the coins on
your sofa can change the world?
- We have to do something.
- NO.  The girl is a social Titanic.
Friends...
How beautiful it is.
Everything is alright.  I
lose too all the time something.
- My name is Riley.
- My name is Grace.
My name is Bree.
When you put all the values ​​together,
they create something beautiful.
Self-Conception.
- I am a good person.
- That makes Riley make a good choice.
13 years of hard work gathered into
what some would call our masterpiece.
Biggest challenge...
- Geez!  We have to fight again.
- That's right.
- How do we score goals?
- With our shots!
- No, we are rushing towards the goal!
- But Grace hasn't scored yet.
Riley controls it.
We threaded the needle!
Come on, Riley.
Like that!  Did you see
that?  That's my daughter!
The foghorns win
the championship!
He shoots, he scores!
Hello girls.
Congratulations on the win.
- That's the coach from high school!
- What a match!
The final attack there? The
three of you are very impressive.
Thank you, Coach Roberts.
I'm late, but whatever the
year I had a three day camp.
I invite the area's best
players.  You have to come along.
Are we dreaming right now?
Pin me right in the arm.
I'm clearly awake.
If we impress him, the three of
us will be on the team next year.
Fire Eagle!  Finally a team
that I support wholeheartedly.
- What did you say?
- Yes!
- We'll be there.
- Big.  Well then, I'll see you tomorrow.
Too wild!
A fun day!
After all, you are a star.  You
get a trainer to slide backwards.
- You got an ice hockey scholarship!
- Dad, stop.  It's just training camp.
Who knows what happened?
28, Anderson.  Leg span.
My expulsion had almost
cost us our victory.
- What if I peek at the camp?
- Do not say that.
- You did well today.
- Appropriate.  Mom understands.
- Looks like I did.
- We are very proud of you.
Good night, monkey.
Yes yes.  Sleep well, darling.
- Riley is very hard on herself.
- But we can make things easier.
I present my super high
technology Riley protection system.
You don't see it.
Here's to all the memories he has in
the back of his head like a penalty box.
It was a burden on him,
so we lightened the burden.
One-way express route to... “We don't
want to think about that right now.”
- Not bad!
- Amazing.
- You take good care of Riley.
- Thank You.  I do my best.
Now we look for the memories.
Here he is waving at a guy who is
actually waving at the girl in the back.
Its bad.  Good choice.
- Here she forgot her maiden name.
- Pretty awkward.
- So what's his name?
- Janet maybe?
It doesn't matter.  Go with him.
We keep the best and
discard the worst.
Good work.  Anger, the rest
smokes in Long Term Memory.
Okay.  Let's eat sleep.
Tomorrow's the big day.
Joy, take it down there,
I think, you do too?
- Do you want to come this time?
- Yes.  I mean no.
Oh no.  This may
not be very good.
Everyone has experienced
this in their value system.
But this is new.  And I
know how important it is.
I don't want to damage anything
or burn it to the ground.
You won't destroy anything.
Have I ever misled you?
- Yes.  Often.
- Come on.
Where I go go, you go.
Geez.
- Mom and dad are proud of me.
- One of the good old ones.
- I'm kind.
- That's good.
I am strong.  I am brave.
I am a very good friend.
I'm a winner.
Together, everyone created
this cherish our Riley.
I am a good person.
What the hell is that?
PUBERTY
- Turn it off, Joy!
- The earth is sinking!
NO!  What are you doing now?
- Problem solved.
- Joy...
OK, we'll clean the
dent. It's demolition day!
- Demolition?  What is going on?
- What is going on?
Who are you?
Do you support this?
SORRY FOR THE FUCK
PUBERTIS IS SOMETHING CRAZY
Are you good for not
tearing Headquarters down?
- There isn't anything.  The permit has just been completed.
- What for?
For expansion, there
is room for others.
- What about the other?
- Are they there yet?
- Margie, do you have the console?
- Yes yes, wait a minute.
- What are you doing now?
- Then he's ready.
Now you have to wake up,
Riley.  You're going camping.
- Lunch break!
- Wait!  You can't escape the chaos.
- We will back.
- Come on.  We're going to be late.
Riley, aren't you packing yet?
You always chase me!  So
leave me alone for one second!
- Are we overreacting a little?
- I barely touched it.
- Flat pan destroys the console.
- What is wrong?
- Mom looks sad.
- I'm the worst person in the world!
- No, then.  Darling.
- I barely touched it.
What did I say?
Let a professional come to you.
I'm too stupid to go
camping or go outside anymore!
Yes, it's clearly broken.
- We prepared for today.
- We agreed to take it easy.
- But he smells.
- Very large!
Stay calm.  Wait with
the agreed script.
You're not stupid,
darling. You just change.
Do you remember that beautiful
one? butterflies in the garden?
- It used to be a caterpillar.
- Alert.
-... by getting wings.
- If you have any questions...
- Mom!  Just go!
A small preview of
the next ten years.
- Riley!
- This will be so fun!
Who's ready for ice hockey camp?
Until we fix the problem, no one
is allowed to touch the console.
So what should we
do this weekend?
We can finally get it
to clean the garage or...
How cool will next year be?
Roberts' team just won every year.
And Val Ortiz is
their leader now.
Valentina Ortiz's
obsession is out of control.
- He joined the team as a freshman.
- This is very difficult.
We just have to play really well in
camp, then we'll all be Flamehawks!
What's that?  We have one
glance.  I do not like it.
- You're paranoid.
- I never miss a glance.
Zoom in 15 to 33. Slightly
to the right.  Zoom in.
There!
- And?
- He's hiding something.  But what?
- What is he doing?
- He looked into our eyes!
No, not just that.
- I can't see anything new.
- Compare.
Look at yourself.
Riley before, Riley now.
- It is clear!
- But what does that mean?
He knows we're hiding something.
- What happened?
- I do not know!
- I can not take it anymore!
- You spit!
Roberts will not remain
our coach next year.
We have found one
second high school.
Oh no.
Okay.  Good.
- This is not very good!
- Seriously?  How long have they known?
We can't move on to high
school without Bree and Grace.
We can still go for a walk.
And we have the weekend, so we're coming along
for the last time we can play as a team together.
Friends forever, right?
Yes.  Of course.
- I can't wait to get on the ice.
- When will we get the program?
This is very sad.
- Do not be sad!
- No.
Wait while driving.
So here we are.  Here
it looks pretty cool.
And you don't lack a single
assistant coach?  I have time.
NO?  See you later,
in a few days.
- You shouldn't miss us too much.
- Riley, do you have everything now?
- Staff?  Gloves?
- Yes.
- Is your phone charged?
- Yes, it's 50%.  That's fine.
Call if anything
comes up.  I love you.
- Okay.  I love you.
- Don't forget deodorant.
- Mother!
- Hey, hey, monkey.
Okay, now.
It doesn't matter.  We need it.
That's a high school student!  We will
not stand there with red and swollen eyes.
Don't worry, we have plenty of
time to think about it after camp.
Where did Bree and Grace go?
- They're there.
- Aren't those traitors already dead to us?
Our best friend?  NO.
Are you okay?
Behave normally! This
is Valentina Ortiz.
We have to say something.
- Hello.
- Hello.  My name is Val.
Yes, you were the captain and broke records
as a junior.  Your favorite color is red...
- What do we say?
- We're not cool.
- Why are we holding his hand?
- Like me.
Coach has told us about it
you. Riley's from Michigan, right?
- Minnesota, sweet.
- We can't fix Val Ortiz.
Yes, it's me.  Riley
goes good old Michigan.
- Who makes orange consoles?
- I haven't touched it.
- Orange is not my color.
- Not me.
Hi everybody.
I'm your big fan.  And
now I stand opposite you.
How can I help?
I can take notes, drink coffee,
manage your calendar, watch you sleep.
You may have wild energy! Maybe
you could just stay in one place.
Whatever.  I AM
always here for you.
- Love it.  What's your name?
- Oops, I forgot that.
I'm Anxious.  One of
Riley's new Feelings.
We're proud to be Here.
Where do I put my things?
- What do you mean by "we"?
- Only I am as tall as you.
- Who are you?
- I envy.
- Wow!  Good hair.
- Forget it.
Look at his hair!  we
should have hair like that.
I like the red
color in your hair.
What are you doing now?
When I join the team, may I
also color it completely red.
- What kind of man is that?
- What is your name, big bun?
That's Flove.  He doesn't like
eye contact and doesn't talk much.
But he is very funny.
Welcome to Headquarters, Flove.
Yes, we are making... No.
Not high.
Your palms are quite sweaty.
Should we be followed?  Then
you can meet some Flamehawks.
Very interesting!  But
we shouldn't show him that.
Yes, quite good.
- What is that feeling?
- That's Ennui.
Wh-what?
Ennui.  That's all, you
will be called boredom.
Come here, An-way!
Did I say that right?
An-waa?  NO.  Nickname!
I just call you Oui-Oui.
NO.
- How do you control it?
- By application.
Stop it!  Now that's enough.
The new feeling can at
first seem very rarely used
- and you just want to say to
them: "Why are you so annoying?"
But I've learned that everyone's
emotions are good for Riley.
- Even this lump.
- OK, good enough.
- Cold.  Previously.
- Take your things and follow me.
- What about our friends?
- Elections are our future.
So agreed.  We should make new friends,
so we won't be alone in high school.
- Not really, Joy?
- Possible...
Wait.  Thank you for
showing me around.
- Why did you do that?
- Excuse me.  What am I doing?
- We left our best friend.
- But we have to go out and meet new people.
The next three days should
be about Bree and Grace.
The next three days can decide
the next four years of our lives.
That's too much.
- Joy is really old fashioned.
- What?
You make Riley happy.
Sad makes him sad.
Fear protects against that
scary thing, he can see-
- and I protect from scary
things, he can't see.  I think ahead.
Now you just have to see it.
I use it as a cup holder.
My team has processed all the data.
We estimate the following scenario:
If we're just messing
around with Bree and Grace-
- not that Riley is
cool in Val's eyes.
He didn't impress the coaches, wouldn't survive
the Flamehawks and then come to high school-
- where he was alone, eating alone,
and only the teacher knew his name.
- The two of us will become good friends.
- This is a sad story.
This is an amazing story.  Love
your energy, but you're way out.
- None of this will happen.
- If you say so.
Do you remember when we all
finally made it to Headquarters?
– It's been 30 seconds, Nostalgia.
- Yes, that was the time.
Nostalgia, you must not
have reached here yet.
You have ten years to come, two graduations
and a wedding.  I have to speak up.
Focus!  Val leads us
into the sacred halls.
Here he is!
The girls are so cool!
And older.  We dress not
about being in front of them.
In the dressing room
there is mutual respect.
- You should meet the other Flamehawks.
- Keep going?
- Hello.
- Riley is from Michigan.
- OK, we'll keep it that way.
- Where are you from in Michigan?
- What now?
- Then we have to ride it until it runs out.
- Michigan cities...
- We have to think of something.
- A little here and there.
- Good.  See you on the ice.
- Do you want to sit with us?
- He wants to sit with us!
Everything is beautiful!
What about Bree and
Blessing?  We sat there.
I will make room for that
my friends.  Thank You.
- Yes alright.  Okay.
- It wasn't that difficult then.
No, that decision will be taken later,
don't bother us for the rest of our lives.
- It is a lie!
- Bree and Grace!
There he is!
Then it's time to cheer!
Say...
Well done, ladies.  Fall.
Joy?
- Wait! Wait!
- Miss!
“Fall” means “fall to
rest." You have to listen.
So now I need your
cell phone.  All of them.
You are here to work, not to play
around.  Are you there, Andersen?
Yes, coach.
Put your phone in the box.
You'll get it again after camp.
His coach took it
quite seriously.
- Maybe I can help...?
- No, thank you.  Not now.
Yes, right?
Do you think this is funny?
You know what's also fun? Penalty
round.  Get on the ice, ladies!
- Well done, Michigan.
- Thank you very much, new girl.
- Good job, Joy.  Now he fits clearly.
- Thank you, Oui-Oui.
- You are behind, Andersen!  Faster!
- This is the most disappointing.
Well done, ladies.  That's small
breathing room.  And then we formed a team.
- His Michigan girls got off to a bad start.
- Are they talking about us?
He won't make the team, if
he doesn't control himself.
As if you were in control of
everything in the first year?
- I'm not very mature.
- You put a straw in your nose.
Now I have to do it, big bun.
I always dream of those people talking
about us.  But it's not like that.
Joy, what do we do now?
- We can just...
- I have an idea.
If we complete our side's
Val, everything will go well.
- Election?
- Hey, Riley.  What is it?
Excuse me.  I will not give
penalty rounds to the whole team.
I feel bad.  I appreciate you
and will never ruin it for you.
- You apply it a little thickly.
- You are just an excellent captain...
- I really admire you.
- OK, OK.  Thank You.
Coach was tough on you today, but
that just means you're on his radar.
- Do?
- Good, you come and talk to me.
- We should try to get into the same team.
- Cold.
Wow.  Only I can do that.
Nothing special. I
just want to help.
Agree.  So that's great, Angst.
I step back, you step in and get Riley
on the right track.  Now I'm active again.
- That's just the first part of the plan.
- Is there a second part?
A good plan has several parts.
Now we form teams
for the rest of camp.
Split yourself down the middle.  Team
one to the right, hold two to the left.
- Now we do it!
- Again in the same team.
- Val wants us!
- But we made a promise to Bree and Grace.
We have to think ahead.
Come on, Riley, move your feet. Val
is on team one, step aside.  Come on.
He gave his friends a
lift.  He wouldn't break it.
You're right, Joy.
What are you doing now?
NO!  You shouldn't
take that.  Put it again.
Not to hold it against
me, but it has to go.
- NO.
- Change is scary, but look here.
I look forward to it.
Welcome to the team, Michigan.
- That's not Riley.
- This is a better Riley.
Riley won't be alone next year.
We build a new self-concept
on him.  The new Riley.
NO!  You shouldn't take
it down there with him.
It will be mine
dead, a burnt corpse!
I am so sorry.  I am looking
forward to this collaboration.
- What are you doing now?
- Riley's life is more complicated now.
This requires more sophisticated
emotions. He no longer needs you, Joy.
- How dare you?!
- You can't just lock us up like that.
Great idea!
I can't breathe!
It's not forever.  Only until
Riley would be 18, or maybe forever.
- We will see.  See you!
- Afraid!  Riley needs us!
Don't worry, Riley.
You are in good hands.
Now we change
everything about you.
Quick question.  How to build
us a new Riley, cool concept-
- if it took 13 years
to build the old one?
The good news is that we
are not starting from scratch.
- I want to plant it too!
- Next time.
If I'm a Flamehawk,
I'm not alone.
No, no, no.
- So set us free!
- Stop!  Shut us up!
Oh, joy...
BOX
We'll be like that here forever!
- Where are you taking us?
- Know Riley's secret.
- We're not a secret.
- Yes yes.
- "This is a big misunderstanding."
- We've never heard of it before.
We are suppressed emotions!
- Shut us up!  Now!
- No, Riley will probably handle it.  Overall.
Hello.  Do you know what we call
that? Denial.  Can you say "denial"?
Hello friends.
WELCOME.  How wonderful it is
to have you here with us today.
- It's Blubber!
- Of that show Riley watched when he was four?
Appropriate.  And
here's a little secret.
Riley can still be
like the program.
step like an
elephant, travel like a
mouse, let's quickly
get to Blubber's house
Kill me.
The bubble that covered US.
Can you help us get out of here?
We will need your
help. Can you free them?
- Who are you talking to?
- My friends.
Can you see the key?
I can't do that either.
- We're done.
- That far.
Welcome to your eternal destiny.
- Spear Sword?
- After all, he plays computer games.
- What is she doing here?
- Riley is secretly in love with him.
If I understand the reason.
I long to be a hero, but
darkness haunts my past.
I understand.
- Who's this?
- It's Riley's Dark Secret.
What's the secret?
You don't want to know that.
An anarchic feeling has
taken over Headquarters.
- If you just opened the jar...
- Children, now we have to learn Latin.
Know Iquid pro quo?  We'll get you
a jar, if you get us out of the box.
No, Blubber.  We are
not masters of their fate.
We were all thrown into this place and remain
thrown away because we don't belong, we're useless.
You don't have to say that!  You
don't deserve to be kicked out.
Wait a minute, Lance.  Remember
the so-called power moves.
- Now I'm going to chase you, Riley!
- Well, so you think so?  Look here!
Frankly!
Listen to me, Lance Slashblade.
No one is completely useless.
But I am a warrior cursed
with a pheasant attack.
Then make your own
curse on your gift.
Protect yourselves, friends,
for I will set you all free!
Can we get help?
Well done, Dark Secret. Now
it's your turn to help us.
My belt bag contains what we can
get out Say after me: "Oh, Bagesen!"
"Oh, the Wallet!"
- Hi everybody.  I'm Taskesen.
- The bag, we want to escape.
- Do you have anything that can help us?
- I have a lot.
What do you think you can do that
is best used?  A tomato?  A frog?
- Or a stick of dynamite?
- You gods!
Hooray!  We did it!  Now sing
us all the song "We did it".
- Continue!
- Thank you friends.  I might...
I have to leave you.
What About Dark Secrets?
Not yet.
That's probably
best for everyone.
- Who let you out?  With you!
- What are we doing?
Oh, you're disgusting.  As you thought
of me, now I will believe in myself.
What?
What happened?
- Dave, help!
- Wait a moment!
Dave!
MY HAT
Spear!
Goodbye friends.
Good afternoon, fate!
There is one more lid for
each jar.  Already come!
- What are we doing?
- Angry, stop it!  Where are you going?
To Headquarters...
to help Riley!
Riley wasn't up
there. He's out there.
We can't go back
without his concept.
How about we go to the
Back Head? Are you crazy?
Enjoy how...
Stop!  Nobody moves!
Do you have a plan?
- Angst probably has a really good plan.
- Of course I have a plan.
He wasn't the only one there
thinking ahead.  First we just need…
Give me a moment.
We follow the Stream
of Consciousness.
- Then we sail all the way to Baghovedet.
- Where are the bad memories.
There we find that
Riley, we know and love.
We put in space Self-Concept,
and Riley will be Riley again.
– That plan could really work.
- Yes!
And then I said to Angst:
“You shouldn't worry too much."
And he would say, “I never
thought about it.  Thank You!"
- Then we hugged and became friends.
- And I'll take it down.
- Not angry.
- Good.  I didn't pry.
Don't worry, I know how to power.
Triste and I have been here before.
- Joy, this is a dead end.
- It's just the worst alley!
Everything changed so fast.
- We're lost.
- If it's fun, you're not lost.
- Nobody thought it was funny.
- Nonsense.  Look how much fun Triste is having.
- I think you know the way.
- I am willing.  Moment.
- He doesn't know the way.
- We're trapped here!
Riley was awake.
It's still too early.  What did they do
him with?  Come on, we'll find another way.
Don't worry, Riley.
We'll be there.
- Why do we get up so early?
- Because we have to speed up a little, mon ami.
So we're going to get on the ice early and
practice like we've never practiced before.
- Aren't we fine?  - Yes.
- But the Flamehawk is really good.
- Appropriate.
Every time we miss, we take it
around.  Ice hockey is not a game.
- Like!
- It was amazing.
We have to be that good
all the time.  Again.
- I'm not the only one who likes to be fresh in the morning.
- It's Val!  We got the same idea.
We're almost the same.
We became good friends.
- How long are you here?
- About an hour.
- I want extra time on the ice.
- Me too.
He understands us!
I've told the others that you have to take
control of everything.  You know what it takes.
Check us out.
This went smoothly.
- Yes.  But Val sure likes us a lot.
- Ask Val lots of questions.
- People like to talk about themselves.
- How was your first year as a Flamehawk?
So it's a tough job.
As in very difficult.
- But I met my best friend.
- Val shares something with us!
We were on a night out and
ordered takeout.  Come with me.
Invitation exclusive.
We will go with you!
- According to you?
- Of course.  Will be fun.
Well done, ladies.
Then we warm up.
- Hey, Riley.
- Hello.
- We don't share Val with them.
- Morning makes me very hungry.
- I'd die for a slice of pizza now.
- Yes!
I said I know the way.
Stream of consciousness.
- But...
- Wow, he's hungry!
- Eat something delicious!
- Deep Pizza!
- And it's still warm.
- With added cheese!
- Sad, come on.
- Listen.  We couldn't take the tube home.
- Only if they activate us with the console.
- We're stranded here.
- Anxiety must be thinking about that.
- I doubt that.  Good.  Okay.
Someone has to climb that
pipe, go home to Headquarters -
- and take us back.
- I did that.  I destroyed it...
- Zero.
- Listen.
- Not you at all.
- Thank You.
- Should I put a hose in it?
Forget it.
- Oh no.  Not me.
- Yes, Sad!  You can.
You're an expert on consoles.
You know the manual by heart.
You say so, but I know a lot
less about manual 28, chapter 7-
- "Remembering objects without
for memory" than people think.
There you prove my
point.  Sounds like yes.
- Where are you?  Are you taking a break now?
- Walkie talkie!  Here.  Can you hear me?
Green light from Glæde.  Shift.
We'll signal when we get there.
And then you got us back.  He's
the quickest way to Headquarters.
I can't.  I'm not
strong like you.
I know you, Sad.  You're strong.
I don't have a specific
one for example, but you can.
- Don't look down.  Just crawl.
- Yes.  I can do that.
- He can handle it.  No?
- 50% chance.
Do you want one?
We hate those bars. It
tastes like cardboard.
- We can't say no to Val.
- You are absolutely right.
- We eat what Val eats.
- That's how it should sound.
Envy, you're in the zone.
Bear with me for a moment.
- He chose me!  Did you see it, Ennui?
- You care too much about everything.
The texture is interesting.
It feels like... What
does that remind me of now?
Cardboard box?
Asparagus?  Broccoli?
- What did they do to him up there?
- Don't know.  But we have to go.
- I didn't step...
- Yes.  Riley needs us.
Okay!
Clumsy.  I thought
I was going to vomit.
If I'm good at ice
hockey, I make friends.
- Good, Miss Riley.
- That's right, Michigan.
You have practiced well
today.  Now relax tonight.
Now comes the best!  Partying
with Val and our future lovers!
Why do we stop here?
There it is.  Red Notebook.
- Now you scared him.
- Why does that scare me?
All the coach's thoughts about you still
apply in that one.  The good and the bad.
- Will you join the team.
- Or not.
- That's too much.
- We only tell the truth.
- What did he write about us?
- Do you think it's something bad?
Not until now!  Imagine if we
weren't on the favorites list.
Or we stand at the top
of the exercise list.
Or worse: We don't stand on any
of the lists and are invisible!
- Sorry, but they're leaving now.
- We lost them.
A comfortable first night with
the group.  Be completely natural.
- Why do we swing our arms like that?
- Keep your arms still.
- It looks too crazy!
- Go as Dani.  The arms are rhythmic.
- Now you are making things worse!
- Yes, sorry, actually I was trying something!
- What do you think the pouch is for?
- Ennui, I'm proud of you.
They laughed.  Does anyone know
what cool people are laughing at?
We are busy with weapons.
Let's just say we get the joke.
- Anger filled all the broccoli.
- Scared, what's wrong?
- I'm not happy with this ship.
- When do we get there?
- We were there when we were there.
- Anxiety will find out soon.
He knows everything, right?
I don't like his
words or actions.
- But I think I can change it.
- Who likes banana cake?  Hands on!
Well, Michigan, what
is your favorite band?
Everyone looked at us.  There
is only one correct answer there.
Rise and Shine!
They are too fat.
I was just them completely
crazy in seventh grade.
- Do you?
- I am a Glow Girly.
NO!  That's definitely something
some of them think is cool.
Remember everything
we know about music.
We definitely know a cool song.
- Fresh Tripelmint -
makes the smile white
Flove, get rid of it!  There
must be something here, somewhere.
Something better, something
Cool.  No, not that one.
We don't have anything better!
There are dad's jingles and soft rock.
You still can't be like
Rise and Shine, right?
Do not panic.
What are we doing?
If we don't like their
music, we are nothing to them.
- We are considered as candidates.
- Excuse me.
I've been waiting all
my life for this moment.
Of course.  I love
Rise and Shine.
Love Rise and Shine.
Avoid broccoli!
- Joy!
- Reach out your hand.
- What's that?
- It's a Sarcasm Gap!
It can open several
kilometers!  Run for your life!
Sarcasm gap?  Seriously?
Rise and Shine is
my favorite band.
He likes Bangun and Binar.  They
create their own choreography.
Joy if we don't follow the moment,
we don't know where we end up.
And if we don't know,
we can't go with the flow!
This is a vicious circle of
tragedy and its consequences!
- We can also ask them there.
- We can do it too.
How lucky we are
that we found you!
that we met you.
Come on!  We really
need your help!
We really need your help.
- What's their problem?
- You just need to increase the charm.
Hello!  You are guaranteed to be the
coolest crane operator in the whole world!
They're just some thugs.
Rise and Shine is very cool.
What are you talking about?
You do love Rise and Shine.
Hello there.
Why do we do best friends
hang out all the time?
We were just at a
concert with them.
- Yes, yes, but...
- But what?
- That was really fun.
- Grace, you're not helping.
Oh yes, what a night indeed.
Cool night.
- Why don't they let him?
- What are we doing now?
We took the longest and best
path.  Good for calf muscles, Vrede.
Best night of my life.
- Nice conversation.
- Very.  But we slipped.
OK, hi.
- This band is very good.
- Michigan has good taste.
If we like the same things as
they do, we have enough friends.
- Good night.
- Yes, I also want to sleep now.
There are lots of hours.  And you should have
some sleep before tomorrow's practice game.
- We always have a practice match on the last day.
- This is how Val joined the team in his first year.
Val scored two goals.  It was true
that no freshman had ever done it before.
On paper, it's not a selection
until next year, but that's it.
- You have to do well.  Be yourself.
- We can be Flamehawks tomorrow.
How are we doing when
our new Self is not ready?
You say something.  we have
to go down with these memories.
Is that broccoli?
- We'll go deeper.
- Well observed.
The longest road is longer than
expected.  How about we sing for a while?
- I know a song: "I surrender".
- We can also play silent games.
One, two, three, calm down.
- We went back and took him down...
- Get angry, not now.
It didn't work.  The real Riley is
out there and we will never find him.
I will find it.  I
just lack visibility.
- OK, that won't work, fine enough.
- It's hopeless.
- We have to drop it and come back.
- This is an increasingly blind road.
Since the puberty alarm went
off, nothing here has worked!
I can no longer recognize the
place.  Sunny at one in the morning!
Never in my life have
I done so many jars.
The Riley we know is gone!
If Joy can't see that,
then it's self-deception.
Self-deception?
Of course it's
just self-delusion!
It takes desperately to maintain optimism, when all
there is is mumbling, mumbling, mumbling from you!
For seven sour Sørensen lemons!
Do you think I have all
the answers? Of course not!
We can't even find
it on our own Backhead.
The fear is valid.
Riley doesn't have much
need for us because he has it.
And it hurts.  Really painful.
The joy you have committed
to many mistakes.  Lots.
And you will commit
even more in the future.
But if you let mistakes stop you,
can we just lie down and give up.
Sounds pretty good.
Come on.
- You can't use it!
- Riley Crisis.
- Thank You.
- Get!
- Forget it, it just happened.
- So agree.
See.
We are right behind you.
Very good.  The flame
eagle has accepted us.
But what's the point if
we don't make the team?
- Tomorrow is very important.
- We have to get more help.
- Ennui, are you listening?
- NO.
- Embarrassed?
- Nice conversation.
- Very.  But we slipped.
- OK, hi.
What am I looking for?
Don't you just hate it when you
forget what you were going to do?
- We need all the help we can get.
- Agreed.
This is our life the
most important game.
Good friend.  It was
going to be a long night.
Now we are preparing the team.
Already come!  We just
need to go through…
Fantasy world
Fantasy world! INSIDE
would love this!
There's Pomfritskoven
and Skyby and...
There's definitely
something going on here.
- Mount Crushmore?
- Are these the four people he likes the most?
- Only Lance is important.
- At least that's the bright side.
- All sides are good sides.
- The rumors?
- The best gossip magazine.
- Latest news!  Hot gossip from Ryugtemøllen!
- "There is a jacuzzi in the teacher's room"?
- "Lucy from the math team is a psychic"?
"Abbie R texts Mike T, but
Mike T bakes cakes at Sarah M"?
- Where are their ethics?
- Pudehyggeborg is still here!
It even got bigger.
And orange?
22: Riley breaks his leg and
disappoints the entire team.  Very good.
18: Val and Dani whisper together, as
Riley misses a goal-scoring opportunity.
We have to help Riley
by getting ready.
Now we ship everything
that can go wrong.
We think ahead.  On everything
he might have done wrong.
Come on, 17. I don't
see anything from you.
Riley missed a scoring
opportunity. Coach took note.
More than that!
Oh no.  They use Riley's
Imagination against him.
Val and the others like us now,
but what if we don't make the team?
We go to number three.
Bree and Grace's team
won and we were laughed at.
22. Val delivered
to us and we burned.
He couldn't do that against
Riley!  We have to stop it.
Beautiful, 37. Riley shoots
the puck in his own net.
- Why did you draw a hippo?
- I'll draw Riley!
- You forgot the ponytail.
- I like the ponytail.
Riley scores a goal and everyone
hugs him?  81, that doesn't help.
Riley's nail polish matches the game
jersey.  Everyone imitates his cool style.
- Riley wears knee pads.
- We buy flowers for the losers.
- What?  I can't always make a profit.
- I love it.
Nail polish?  Knee pads? You
don't seem to understand the task.
What...
- Who sent that screenplay to Riley?
- How could I possibly know?
What happened?  Who sent
all this positive stuff...
Joy.  I know you are there.
- Is that him?
- Joy from Headquarters?
The police thought
they were on their way.
- We tried it.
- Don't listen to Fear.
He uses a bad scenario
to change Riley.
I did it for you.  So
Riley could be happier.
If you want him to be happy,
will you stop torturing him.
Who is with me?
Seriously?  There isn't any?
- Sorry, Joy.
- Yes!  You're onto something, 87.
A cat.  Not very
clear, but good enough.
Who has anything?  Come on!
If Riley was better than
Val, Val would hate him.
Or Riley is better than
Val, and Val respects him.
Yes!  Like that!
What if Riley is so bad he has to
stop playing ice hockey altogether?
What if he plays, so his coach is
touched and he will go to the Olympics-
- and he achieved a home
victory to the joy of the nation?
Stay in the real
world for a moment.
NO!
Fear has chained you to the
table and made you draw nightmares!
You don't need to do it
anymore find yourself in it!
Put down the pencil!
Stop the scenario!
- Hah!
- Now that's enough!
- My scenario!
- Pillow fight!
For Riley!
We have to be prepared.
NO!
- OK, we should continue.
- Agreed.
- Come on, bastard!
- NO.
- Return!
- To the Possible Careers Parade!
Grab a balloon!
- Pastry chef!
- Underpaid!
- Art teacher!
- Not appreciated!
- Music ethnologist!
- Don't understand what it is.
- Supreme Court Judge!
- Yes!
Return!
They escaped!
Like!  Now Riley can sleep.
I miss the jar!
Joy doesn't understand.  Without a
scenario we are not prepared to face it.
Tomorrow's match
is very important.
Coaches turn us into Flamehawks
or condemn us to a lonely future.
If only we knew what
the coach thought of us.
- Notebook!
- Brilliant idea!
It says all the coach's
thoughts about you.
We snuck into his
office and read it.
Come on, Riley.  Move your feet.
- Is not it?
- Are we pushing it too hard?
Read it visually in that notebook!
Then we know what we need to improve.
Riley, no.
Joy?  Come on in, Joy.
Sad?  What is wrong? Why
did Riley wake up again?
Anxiety causes Riley
to barge into the coach.
- He knows better than that.
- Yes, when he regains his self-image.
Sad, stop him.
But don't stay trapped
in it.  Changed!
No, Riley.
Why did he stop?
Sad?  Ennui! Where's
your cell phone?
My cell phone?  Where's that?  Seriously!
This is not the case.  No, no, no!
He must be here
somewhere.  Find him.
That's it, I got you!
Sad...
NO.
It felt wrong that
Riley was hanging around.
Riley wasn't like that.
It's not about who Riley
is, but who she will become.
Andersen: NOT READY YET
- "Not ready"?
- Has the choice been made?
- Aren't we going to form a team?
- We have one more day.
What we can do?
What will Val do?
We have to make the coach change
his mind.  We need ideas.  Lots.
Oh no.  This is brainstorming!
Too close!
Give you the puck?
Ruining another team?
Yes!
Bad ideas don't contact Riley.
Joy!
Destroy as many as possible!
I caught the idea
I wish it was mine.
NO!  None of them are
good enough!  Get more!
Jump on the balloon!
It's worse than broccoli!
Take ideas!
- The ideas are too small.
- We need bigger ideas.
This is our salvation!
Clear?
We need this idea!
If Riley takes it between
them, something is wrong!
The only way out is up.
That is a good idea!
I like that one.
Oh no.
Hold me!  I mean!  Hold me!
Scared, do you have a parachute?
Yes, yes.  Why should
none of you be with him?
- Solid ground!  And good landing.
- We did it!
We did it!  Already come!
We're going to Baghovedet.
You're done, Anxiety!
The coach was right.  Riley wasn't ready.
But we are very close to the new Riley.
We missed it here.  We showed
them that we are fearless Flamehawks.
Cherry sports drink
- Finally we are one of them!
- What do you think, Triste?
- I...
- Cold!
- Red is really our color.
- Very pleasant!
OK, that creates
jealousy.  Excuse me.
They think cool is temperature.
Hey, Michigan.  You're the one
riding on the red wave, right?
- We're coming in.
- I hope it's okay.
I'm not a Flamehawk yet, but I just
want to match the rest of the team.
- That's fine.  Did you sleep last night?
- No, not with today's big game!
- Practice match?
- I said, you made him angry.
You're in the zone, right?
- Get ready to score.
- Overall!
Val scored two goals in a practice match and
became a Flamehawk.  What's better than two?
- Three!
- Three!  We said that at the same time.
But how can we
score three goals?
Riley just did it all.  And I think
this one is the icing on the cake.
Moment.
Come on!
We are very close.
Self-concept above that bj...
- There are some.
- I haven't sent back that much.
- When he entered the glass doors at the party.
- And when he broke grandma's plate.
Well, these memories
are not part of him.
There it is!
- I am a good person.
- Oh no.
Yes.  Come on.
Here he is!
I'm not good enough.
- What?
- I'm not good enough.
I'm not good enough.
Are you sure...?
He just knew that there was
still room for improvement.
He is fine.
Sadly, we have a
Self-Conception.
Get us back.  sad,
can you hear us?
I'm not good enough.
I can fix it.  I had to
simply recalibrate the console.
No more surprises.
OK, it should be here, and it's
there.  And not quite there, but here.
We're stepping it up a
bit here. Then fine tune.
The person who was set
up was completely wrong.
Sad, now!
- Joy!
- Oh no!
I am a good person.
I'm not good enough.
- It's the only way back.
- We are very close.
Joy!
Where are you going?
28, Anderson.  Leg span.
28, Anderson.  Seatbelt!
I expected more from you, Riley.
Not that...
What...
Come on.
What am I not seeing?
I am a good person.
Joy.
What are we doing now?
I do not know.
I don't know how
you stop Anxiety.
Maybe we can't do it.
Maybe it's always like
this when you get older.
You feel less happy.
But I am sure of one thing.
Riley would never be himself if we didn't
bring him here to Headquarters.  Quickly.
How?
- Good fight, Riley.
- Thank you, and the same for you.
I'm not good enough.
Yes!  Come on, come on, come on!
Riley, I'm free!  Deliver!
I'm not good enough.
- Well done, Michigan!
- Just save a little for all of us.
Like!  The first of three goals.
How do we get our
self-perception from here to there?
I have an idea, but I
really don't like it.
Angry, Riley needs us.
Oh, the Bag!
What are you waiting
for?  Now say the words!
Oh, the Bag!
Hi everybody.  I am the Bag!
- We know that well.
- We're going to Headquarters.
- Do you have anything that can help us?
- I have a lot of things.
What do you think is the best?
Rolls of tape, ducks...
Continue!
Seriously, Wallet?  Dynamite?
Don't you have one?
jetpack or plane?
Do you think I have
everything here?
I offer you a bath
duck and duct tape.
Now I have it.  But we
have to use more dynamite.
Do you know?  Good luck.
Come on!  Take the puck!
Take!
I'm not good enough.
What are you doing now?
We are on the same team!
Yes!
Dani might have been a little angry with us,
but everyone forgave us when we joined the team.
Come on, Riley.  One more goal.
Wait a minute, Joy.
Do we blow up the rock?
And returning to Headquarters
amidst an avalanche of bad memories?
How do we avoid these bad
memories creating bad values?
I do not know.
What is wrong?  I join.
- Ready?
- For Riley.
- Now we do it.
- We're coming now, Riley.
Jump!
Come on!
Dirt!
- I'm not good enough.
- You have to score!
- Andersen, penalty box, two minutes.
- NO!
Grace, are you okay?
- We hurt Grace.
- It went very fast.  I do not see it.
- I'm not good enough.
- What have I done?
Oh no.  I fixed
that.  I'll fix it.
I expected more from you, Riley.
NO!
Already come.
I'm not good enough.
Come on, Riley.
Control yourself.
Now control yourself.
I'm not good enough.
You have to score, Riley!
Otherwise, everything is in vain.
Afraid, you pushed him too hard.
OK, take a break!
- Sad!
- Joy!  Help!
We can handle it!
- This won't work!
- That's fear.
Scared, stop!
You don't have to
decide who Riley is.
Worry.
You have to let it go.
I am a good person.
Joy.  Excuse me.
I just tried to protect him.
But you're right.  We don't
need to determine who Riley is.
We keep the best and
throw away the worst!
28, Anderson.  Seatbelt!
I am a good person.
What are you doing now?
I'm selfish.
I'm kind.
I'm not good enough.
I am a good person.
I have to adapt but
I want to be myself.
I'm brave, but I feel scared.
Success means everything.  I
committed error.  I'm funny.  I was led.
I am a good friend.  I am a bad
friend. I am strong.  I am weak.
Riley, are you okay?
Yes.  I mean: no.
I really pity you.
When you said you were going to
the second school, I panicked.  And...
I am so sorry.
If you no longer
want to be friends...
... I understand it well.
But I hope that
you can forgive me.
One day.
- Come on, ladies!
- We have to finish the game.
Joy.  Riley wants you.
Riley!
Yes!
Minnesota, your eyes
are glued to the screen.
It's almost two o'clock.
Coach will post the list soon.
- Two o'clock.  He...
- In six minutes.
So what if we don't become one
fire Eagle?  Thanks for asking.
Mom and Dad will
be disappointed.
We will not be ice hockey
players, but musical ethnologists.
- We have no friends and die alone.
- Calm.  None of that is happening right now, is it?
Cold!  Then we sat down
in our very special chairs.
- Yes, that's a good idea.
- Isn't it better now?
Yes, that's the problem.
We can't control whether Riley
joins the team.  What can we control?
Riley has a Spanish test
tomorrow.  We have to go.
- Yes, we really have it...
- Olvidamos!
- What does it mean?
- "Forget".
- Great from the start!
- I never thought about that.
Thank you friends.
And we have followed along well
throughout the elite training.
- I'm the only one who thinks about it.
- That's your idea!
- I envy myself.  Thank You.
- You're welcome!
- Who said that?
- My new friend, Taskesen.
- Confetti if we make a team.
- Great idea.
No matter what,
we love our girls.
Confetti if not!
- Is that an email from the coach?
- No, from Bree and Grace.
Good luck!!
I miss those girls.
- Do you remember when Bree, Grace, and us...
- It was too early!
Then I'll just wait downstairs.
It's three minutes.
You two.  He succeeded.
Because he owns
us! Yes!  Correct?
- Because he... Maybe?
- Well done, Flove!
Just look at Flove!
If it doesn't work out this
year, maybe do it next year.
- Yes.
- I like our girl.
- Can you do something else?  He is very fast.
- And good at ice hockey.
- He's creative.
- He can bore us, but never boring.
He could now be a
little sarcastic.
He can have real bad ideas.
Sometimes it is true
that something is wrong.
And sometimes he is
too hard on himself.
But all of Riley's
pages shape who he is.
And we love everything
about our girl.
Each one is messy,
on the beautiful side.
OK, Secret Deep Darkness.
The time has come.
It doesn't matter.
Come out with you.
Okay.  just get out there,
mate.  What's the secret?
- We make holes in the carpet.
- Is that all?
I think we peed in
the pool.  No, wait.
And he left.
Riley how did he go to camp?
We have agreed that
we tell them everything.
- Also we sneak into the office?
- And Grace's tough tackle?
- Protest.
- Excuse me.  Excuse me.
It went well.
He's gone for three days,
and we only get "fine"?
What does the red number
mean, is he a gang member?
Welcome back, Angst.
He's gone for three days,
and we only get "fine"?
This might cover it
well. Back to the fight.
Nice pass to Reeves,
and then down the middle.
To the limit. What a brazen act!
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/njd83
Help other users to choose the best subtitles